<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://jgood.io" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><title>JGood</title><link>https://jgood.io</link><description>Personal blog</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 13:02:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><generator>clj-rss</generator><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2021-02-20-poc-pod-notes</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2021-02-20-poc-pod-notes</link><title>🗒️ A POC for taking Roam notes on audio</title><description>My podcast player used to include the current position with the export from the share feature. When it was removed, for whatever reason, it kind of ruined my note process. I like to take quick notes with the position so I can revise by listening back whenever I get around to it. Now I have to include the position manually when I export to Roam's quick capture screen. It's an annoying context switch.This problem got me thinking about taking notes on audio in general . There isn't a good solution for the niche of second brain users. I want Roam and Notion integrated directly in the player for seamless note taking without context switching. I actually have the skills needed to build this, so I made a Proof of Concept over a weekend.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-12-20-failed-gesture-experiment</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-12-20-failed-gesture-experiment</link><title>❌ Failed Gesture Experiment</title><description>GistI had an idea for a complicated set of gestures for an app I'm working on. Not being sure how it would work I made an experiment app to test it out. Ran into two problems so I'm tossing the whole idea.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-12-20-video-production-notes</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-12-20-video-production-notes</link><title>📽️ Video Production Notes</title><description>WhyI made a goal to write 3 blog posts before 2020-12-21 and this is the third. It's a note compilation from watching videos on youtube about video production. Everybody is starting a youtube channel so I've shared this multiple times. I figured it would make a nice post.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-10-25-memento-mori</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-10-25-memento-mori</link><title>💀 Memento Mori Life Chart Experiment</title><description>InspirationI came across two websites with a visualization of a 90 year old life measured in weeks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-09-03-playing-with-vega-lite-pt-1</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-09-03-playing-with-vega-lite-pt-1</link><title>📈 Vega-Lite Fun Pt-1</title><description>I'm obsessive about tracking personal metrics, and I want to make data visualizations. This is an initial attempt at exploring my own data, and Vega-Lite as a tool to visualize it. I'm using Oz as a Vega-Lite wrapper because the setup was easy.Final product</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-04-05-stealing-with-deps</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-04-05-stealing-with-deps</link><title>💎 Stealing with deps.edn</title><description>This builds on a previous post about a template repo I made. The goal was to make it easier for me and others to start a project on this stack. The ideal state wasn't a repo that needs manual setup. The ideal state is one command that generates a ready to run project. This post will describe how I made an npm module called create-expo-cljs-app.The Target</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2020-01-26-expo-shadow-cljs-starter</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2020-01-26-expo-shadow-cljs-starter</link><title>A template for Expo apps with Shadow CLJS</title><description>Do you want to make a native app? Are you familiar with a React stack? Do you also want to write in Clojure? Then the solution is -- Expo with Shadow CLJS. It's an easy technology transition and a well maintained platform to build on. I've used Expo with plain Javascript at my day job for a couple of years. My most significant personal project is an Expo app written in CLJSWhy</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://jgood.io/2019-07-21-hello-world</guid><link>https://jgood.io/2019-07-21-hello-world</link><title>Hello World</title><description>(:</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>